Previously
P’Sunny, he isn't only targeting you.
If I went through the casting,
it will be my first time as a lead actor.
If you still can't find any work for your kids,
you might be let go.
Aren’t you upset for being lured to those old molesters?
You really don't have feelings?
When you're with me, you just need to put all your focus on me.
At the December Hotel.
You'll meet Director Arthur there.
Who are you?
Ugh! Why is it so quiet today?
No one’s coming at all.
Why are you so late today?
You might as well come tomorrow?
Didn’t you say that you don’t have money?
Do you want this job or not?
What do you want me to do today?
Wanna hook up with me upstair?
Yes.
Jeez, you’re no fun at all.
Your costume is over there.
Go change and hand out those flyers.
You have to hand all of them out tonight.
If you can't give it all away, I’m docking your pay.
Opening
Having fun messing with me?
How are you?
Not gonna lie. You look good.
When I got here, there was only this mascot left.
Are you okay with this one?
I can wear whatever they gave me.
Although the look on your face…
Smile a little maybe?
I'm really sorry.
Why?
Sorry about the jump from a perfume ad
to whatever this is.
Why are you sorry?
Work is work.
I can do it.
Um...
Yeah?
After I’m done, can I borrow this mascot for an hour?
I'll hurry to get it back.
Uh, I think so.
But I'll ask them for sure if you can borrow it.
Um, I'm sorry. The one is too tight.
Can we swab outfits?
Is that a rabbit?
Hey come on, come on. The crews get out now.
Slate in.
Ready?
Scene 1, Take 1.
And Action!
A little harder!
Cut! Cut.
Cut, cut, cut.
It still doesn't look…
It still doesn't look synchronized.
Klah! Tell them to put the logo up front.
The crews go and check it out.
Okay.
Continue shooting.
Scene 1, Take 17.
and, Action
Cut!
Give him something to eat.
He must be tired.
Take 18! Action!
Cut!
- Nicely done!
- Awesome. Cut.
Very good. We can proceed now.
The customer asks me to deliver this
to Director Arthur.
Khun Game?
Yes?
What's up?
The customer asks me to deliver this to Director Arthur.
to Director Arthur.
Well, I’m sorry I’m in a hurry.
This one is for you, secretary Game.
Thank you.
If you don’t mind, you can go to the director yourself.
He's in the twenty-first floor meeting room.
P’Mai, can you please give him access to the door?
Alright.
I'm sorry.
The information that I need.
Have you found them?
Not quite yet.
The only information I have is about the person named Jay
and he’s the same person as Director Arthur.
Why?
Shocked because of the fool you tricked standing in front of you?
Are you okay with sleeping with a man?
Ever since I started working in the entertainment industry,
I've never forgotten a sound I heard once.
Don't change the subject.
Say again.
Why are you fooling me?
Don't stop.
Say more.
Did you not understand what I said?
Memories that are locked deeply within us,
all it needs is a little key to unlock it.
Now all the memories come flooding back.
Just the second I saw your mascot costume.
I immediately thought of my favorite voice.
What the fuck are you doing?
Are you screwing with me?
How do you want to do this?
Hey!
If you don't bow to my feet
then get ready to have your face scarred.
Hey, who the fuck is this?
Little Rabbit.
It’s because of you
that took all the fun out of the night.
Me?
Yes!
How are you going to take responsibility for this?
What do you want me to do?
You’re going to make me have fun tonight.
Can you sleep with a man then?
Well, if I’m the one topping you then yes.
Wait. Take it slow.
Yeah, yeah.
Your tattoo,
does it have any meaning?
I’m you if there is any meaning to it?
If you don't want to talk, that's fine.
If you’re done crying then
take the rabbit's head off now.
If you want me to be fond of you,
you'd better do as you're told.
Do you believe in karma?
I don't know what you're talking about.
But I do believe that karma is real.
Let's continue our business.
Sorry.
I don't have time to play with you.
This is for having fun with me.
Damn it.
Are you crazy?
Let me go!
Crazy, huh?
I'm more conscious now than ever.
One more thing.
I'm gonna fool or not fool you.
Director Arthur, the person you've been looking for all along is me.
You blame me for fooling you?
No, not at all.
I never fooled you once.
Because you're crazy stupid
for not knowing who I am.
It must have been so much fun for you.
Well, it's not boring to say the least.
Well If you’re having enough fun
the pay me.
You charged for a nearly done cigarette for 200,000 Baht.
I've been letting you mess with me for almost a month.
It should have cost you your damn arm and that leg.
If you've already paid,
there is no refund policy from me.
Yeah.
I'm going to be paying you for sure.
You have to take my payment method though.
Without any conditions.
If you're thinking about refunding,
I'll be the death of you.
Thank you, P’Kajorn, for this meal.
Yo’re so nice.
Oh, don’t mention it.
We’ve been working so hard so
we should treat ourselves a bit, right?
Thank you again.
Where have you been?
The team is waiting for the mascot.
Can I help you?
It's alright.
I'll handle it myself.
Please, enjoy your meal.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
You're not back yet?
I'm waiting for you.
Although today you did very well.
It’s like you’ve done this before.
Well, I did.
Really?
Are you serious?
I was just joking.
Is there anything that you haven’t done before in your life?
Are you secretly in debt to a loan shark?
That one I was too.
What?
But I paid off all the debt.
Okay.
Well, that's good.
Now, the viewers are smart, you know?
You need to get all the issues sorted out.
So that no one will dig up your pass to ruin your future.
You have tattoo?
Above the buttocks.
What is the meaning of it?
I don't know either.
At that time I liked it, so I just told the artist to give me this one.
Oh, yeah.
Then it probably doesn't mean anything.
Yeah, well…
Have you talked to Sky lately?
Hey, Sky.
Why are you walking here?
The class is starting soon.
Why do you guys have to hurry that much?
Ugh.
There's a guest teacher today. Just come hurry!
Why aren’t you moving?
So this is the portrait that…
Excuse-us?
Please come in.
Portrait photography.
The most important thing is probably a model.
And does anyone know?
What's the most striking thing on the face of a model?
Please.
I don't know.
You don't know?
You're late.
And still trying to mess with me.
Should I take 5 points from you?
The answer is…
The eyes.
Do you know why?
Because the eyes are the windows to the heart.
Let's forget about the theory for now.
You come out and model for me.
Yeah, you.
Does anyone want to help me set up the lighting?
I do.
Okay.
Really diligent.
Really late but diligent.
The lighting in portrait photo,
we have to control it nicely.
So that we can tell the story in one frame.
But don't be afraid of the shadow.
Because this shadow will help us tell a story as well.
Okay.
Will you please move the light this way?
It's set up differently from the lighting used for the video.
This light must be consistent with the actor's performance.
This shadow will help us tell a story better.
Hey!
Does the lesson get to you so deeply?
I'm sorry.
Oh, Sky, what's wrong? Where are you going?
Go, be a model then.
Who would do the light for me then?
Why did you run out like that?
I'm sorry.
I just don't feel well.
Not just because you're afraid of cameras?
I’ve seen you done stage plays before.
I know you have potential.
Although it seems your symptoms,
it's not just like any normal camera fright.
If it affected you that much,
have been secretly filmed before?
If you don't know anything, don't say it.
Go back and shoot your nude photos then.
So it’s true?
Oh, Sun.
I'm going home, do you want me to drop you off?
I already left.
I’m with Director Arthur.
Ah. You’re with Director Arthur.
Huh?
Wait? What did you say?
You’re with Director Arthur?
This manager of yours…
he seems to take good care of his actors.
Oh that’s right.
You haven't answered my question yet.
What is the tallest building in the world?
Burj Khalifa in Dubai.
Seriously,
Why are you asking me these questions?
Ask for what?
Director Arthur
He likes intelligent people.
Intelligent people will win all battles.
Have you ever listened to this song?
What’s up with you?
This song is massly popular.
But you don't know the song.
Then you have to…
Endure to answer any of my questions for a while
Where are you taking me?
I’m heading to work at Alice’s.
But before going there,
I’ll need to make a stop first.
Where?
Let’s go.
I'm hungry now.
You choose what you want to eat.
You want me to choose?
That's right.
If you don't choose?
I can choose now.
So what are you gonna eat?
I choose to eat you.
What are you doing?
You said you'd accept my method of payment
without any conditions.
So… What do you want to eat?
This is your idea of where our first dinner date should be?
You told me to choose.
So I did.
You bastard.
What? You want mustard, unfortunately they don’t have it.
You don't speak English at all?
Yes. No. Okay.
Those are all that I speak.
Excuse me, your Pad Thai is here.
Do you know how to do that?
If you like sour, add lime.
If you like salty, add fish sauce.
If you like spicy, add chili.
Do I really have to teach you that?
And if I like this one?
Your Pad-Thai right?
This has to be the most delicious Pad-Thai.
This is your job tonight.
Try reading this script.
You know, right?
Sunny's about to become a main character in the upcoming series.
The series that will be created by Dream’s.
Mr. Two baht!
Where have you been?
Do you know how much I want to see you?
I also have something to ask you.
What?
Did my Jay take you to that cemetery?
Yes, sir.
That's why I want to know who that woman was.
How can you make my Jay trust you so much?
Probably because
he knows I'm here to avenge Sunny.
Sunny Thanaphat
That smug sucking up actor?
Why?
What was your feud?
That I never knew before.
Did Sunny ever kill your family?
Why do you want to enter this industry?
To take revenge on him.
I'm warning you.
You can't fool me with lies.
I have hawk-like eyesight.
Mr.Songbaht.
I really came to get revenge on Sunny.
Why is that?
Did Sunny really kill your family?
No, sir.
The person who killed the younger and the mother
was me.
When did your mother and brother die?
Five years ago, sir.
Mother died three months after my brother died.
How did they die?
I understand you might be the cause of their deaths,
but can you explain it a little clearer?
Do you believe in karma?
It happened five years ago.
I used to be a debt collector for a loan shark.
Oh! I gave up.
After I got kicked out of school.
I'm sorry to inform you that the institution has fired you.
One day I went to collect the debt.
I hurt his daughter.
Threatened them.
And then took everything from them.
Even their land deeds.
I really took everything from that family.
And karma caught on to me.
That night, he stabbed my brother.
Someday karma will get to you.
You fucking piece of shit.
I had a boyfriend.
His name was Bank but now goes by Sunny.
That night after my brother died,
he disappeared.
With the money I saved up for my mother's treatment.
After that, I borrowed money from a loan shark.
In order to get my Mon a treatment.
From a loan shark's debt collector
Then I went from a debt collector to a debtor.
And then there was one day.
It's been five years since the incident.
I heard of something.
That was unexpected.
I was the one who told that guy
to go down and stab his brother.
About the person who was involved
in my brother and mother’s death.
That's why I
I want revenge on Sunny.
And then
After the people your family died,
What did you do after that?
I paid off my debt, sir.
For five years?
And after that?
Nothing else.
Now I've paid off all my debts.
And I don't want money from that guy.
And what work have you done before?
I’ve done it all as long as it pays my bills.
And in those five years,
how many days have you had you stopped working?
No, sir.
My Jay must know all about you.
People like him must’ve known.
Now I know,
That he is the same person as Director Arthur
Are you..
You know the truth now?
But I still believe thst.
That a kind-hearted person like you
must have a reason that’s why you helped him to hide it from me.
My allergy is acting up.
I'm allergic to dust.
Dusty, dust, dust.
The dust got into my eyes.
That’s why my eyes are so watery.
Don't!
Don't get the wrong idea.
You are…
Aside from being nice, you're also smart.
Now I’ve understood,
Why is my Jay trusting you so much?
He took you to his mother's grave at the cemetery.
My Jay also
came back here wanting vengeance, too.
You still don't know,
who was the first person who founded Dream?
Congratulations, Mrs. Pavinee.
Congratulations to Mrs. Pavinee.
Whatever about Jay's mother
that you know from me today?
Don't tell my jay.
Can I trust you right?
Hey!
Seriously?!
You little punk!
Do you know whose car this is?
Don't you watch where you're going?
Hey!
Let him go.
There's nothing I can do now
in the entertainment industry.
Does that mean you don't want to know
who ruined your audition?
You're gonna have to beg me someday.
The president chose Sunny for reasons
other than his qualifications.
It must be Sunny because the sponsor has asked for him.
Shit!
Get rid of him now.